<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rickGame xmlns:props="pyf.props">
        <attr>
                <name>Braaiinnnssss!!!</name>
                <author>Zack Raver</author>
                <version>1.0</version>
                <description>You awaken to blinding fluorescent lights. You smell rubbing alcohol and disease. You are lying slumped on an operating table.The silence is penetrating and uneasing.</description>
                <!--intro>"You awaken to blinding fluorescent lights. You smell rubbing alcohol and disease. You are lying on an operating table.The silence is penetrating and uneasing."</intro-->
        </attr>

<!--Rick's Game Rooms--> 
<!--################################# Hospital Grounds Classes #####################DONE-->               
        
        <DocOffice name="The doctor's office, Start room, room, Hospital bed room, i6, I6">
                <ldesc>Sitting up, you can see that you are in a simple doctors office. 
                        The walls are blank except for the words: ITs All FUcKED eScape If YOu CAN... carved across the wall near a window to the east. There are cabinets on the north wall. 
                        There is a door to the West. From your position you notice a key has been slid beneath the door.
                </ldesc> 
                
                <exits>
                        <west><DocHallOne /></west>
                        <east>You can see the ocean in the distance. Unfortunately, you'll have to find another way out. Even if there weren't bars on these windows it would be a looong drop.</east>
                </exits>
                
                <Rick name="yourself, Rick"> 
                        <ldesc>You are wearing a hospital gown, though you feel fine.</ldesc>
                        <HosGown name="Hospital gown, gown, scrubs">
                            <ldesc>Sterile and uncomfortable. It also seems to be too small... Maybe I can find some better clothes.</ldesc>
                                <props:Mobile />
                                <props:Wearable>
                                        <attr>
                                                <worn type="bool">True</worn>
                                        </attr>
                                </props:Wearable>                
                        </HosGown>
                </Rick>
                
                <DocKey name="Doctor's key, doc key, key one, key 1, key, door key">
                        <ldesc>The key to the office you are in.</ldesc>
                        <props:Mobile />
                        
                </DocKey>
                
                <DocCabinet name="Doctor's cabinet, cabinet, cubby, cabinets">
                        <ldesc>The cabinets seem to be locked except for one cubby.</ldesc>
                        <props:Container />
                </DocCabinet>
                
        </DocOffice>
                
        <DocHallOne name="Dead end hallway, hallway one, end of hallway, hall, h6, H6">
                <ldesc>Stifling a scream, you quickly realize what your room vandal meant by fucked. The hallway in which you are standing is caked 
                        in blood and bile and the stench is making your head spin. You need to get the fuck out of here. There are double doors to 
                        the north and the hallway continues around the corner to the south.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north>After a shove you realize these doors must be barricaded from the other side. You won't be escaping this way.</north>
                        <south><NurseStation /></south>
                </exits>
        </DocHallOne>
        
        <NurseStation name="Hosital nurse's station, nurse's station, nurses station, hallway two, h7, H7">
                <ldesc>The nurse's station is in disarray. It looks like everyone left in a hurry most of the stretchers are turned over and the floor is 
                        covered in tongue depressors and... pieces of tongue? The doorway to the east is labelled, Stairs, with a green exit sign above it. There is a window with sunlight
                        pouring through it to the west. The doctor's office is to the north.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><DocHallOne /></north>
                        <west>This window is barred too. You can hear faint screams coming from the elementary school beyond the hospital grounds.</west>
                        <east><DocStairwell /></east>
                </exits>
        </NurseStation>
        
        <DocStairwell name="Hopsital stairwell, stairs, stairwell, hopsital stairs, i7, I7">
                <ldesc>The clutter from the hopsital staff's clumsy, panicky flight had spread to the stairway. All the way down the three flights of stairs there were 
                        ladies shoes abandoned and stiff, lab coats strewn off to either side. On the ground floor there is a door to the east and an emergency exit to the
                        south. The Nurse's station is back up the stairs to the west.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><NurseStation /></west>
                        <east><EROne /></east>
                        <south>You push gently on the door and an alarm begins to blare loudly. Your stomache does a flip as a filthy, blood-soaked hand grabs through the cracked door at the sound. After slamming it shut, you realize you've got to get out of here some other way</south>  <!--If walk through here alarm sound and dies, ENDING*****************************-->
                </exits>
        </DocStairwell>
        
        <EROne name="ER exam rooms, emergency exam rooms, er one, j7, J7">
                <ldesc>You step into a series of exam rooms. There are dozens of closed doors and abandoned stretchers stradled with sheet-covered figures. Upon closer 
                        inspection you realize the -dead?- bodies have all been securely strapped to their stretchers. The nearest bed has a pale hand hanging over its
                        side. The stairwell is back to the west and the double doors to the waiting room is to the east. 
                </ldesc>
                
                <erZombieContainer name="Pale hand, bedridden zombie, stretcher, bed hand">
                        <ldesc>The hand is holding something small and plastic.</ldesc>
                        <props:Container />
                </erZombieContainer>
                
                <exits>
                        <north>These exam room doors are all shut and locked from the outside. Is that shuffling on the other side? Better keep moving.</north>
                        <west><DocStairwell /></west>
                        <east><ERWaitingRoom /></east>
                </exits>
        </EROne>
        
        <ERWaitingRoom name="ER waiting room, waiting room, emergency waiting room, k7, K7">
                <ldesc>The waiting room is surprisingly silent and clean-feeling. Nobody likes hospital waiting rooms. Keep moving! The exam rooms are to the west and the doors outside
                        are on the northern wall</ldesc>
                
                <exits>
                        <north><HospitalParkingLot /></north>
                        <west><EROne /></west>
                </exits>
        </ERWaitingRoom>
        
        <HospitalParkingLot name="Hospital parking lot, parking lot, er parking lot, k6, K6">
                <ldesc>The outside world is no better scene than the hospital. The carnival across the street to east has dark plumes of smoke rising from it.
                        It seems that someone has formed a barricade of ambulances and other cars in the parking lot to the west. The hospital is back south and there
                        is a Jack in the Box to the north.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><ERWaitingRoom /></south>
                        <north>You won't be able to fit through the drive-through window, the entrance is beyond the ambulance barricade</north>
                        <west><HospAmbulance /></west>
                        <east><MainStreetSix /></east>
                </exits>
        </HospitalParkingLot>
        
        <HospAmbulance name="Ambulance blockade:Hospital side, ambulance barricade, ambulance, j6, J6">
                <ldesc>The ambulance rocks generously as you climb into it. Nothing exciting in here though it's been obviously looted or all medical equipment. 
                        The driver's side door is open and the back has been crushed against another ambulance, you could probably climb over there.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <east><HospitalParkingLot /></east>
                        <north><JibsAmbulance /></north>
                        <west>This door is jammed against the adjacent car, gotta go out the back or driver's side.</west>
                </exits>
        </HospAmbulance>
        <JibsAmbulance name="Ambulance blockade:Jibs side, j5, J5">
                <ldesc>This ambulance has been looted also. There's nothing here. Except one of the cabinets has been wedged open.
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north>The front window is busted but there is too much broken glass to climb through. Should just use a door.</north>
                        <east><Jibs /></east>
                        <west>This door is locked from the outside. Maybe there is a key nearby<!--PharmacyParkingLot /--></west> <!--SHOULD BE BLOCKED OR LOCKED OR SOMETHING*************************************-->
                        <south><HospAmbulance /></south>
                </exits>
        </JibsAmbulance>
        
        <Jibs name="Jack in the box, restaraunt, Jibs, k5, K5">
                <ldesc>America's finest. The restaurant is empty, luckily. You do hear some moaning coming from the back. The kitchen to the south is empty except for the disgusting smell of 
                        un-rotten fast food and the drive through window. The mysterious ambulance blockade is the west and the main doors lead out to the north.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><JibsAmbulance /></west>
                        <north><JibsParkingLotExit /></north>
                        <south>Peering through the drive-through window you see the hospital lot is filling up with people...unhealthy looking people. Definently not going back there.</south>
                </exits>
        </Jibs>
        
        <PharmacyParkingLot name="Pharmacy parking lot, pharmacy lot, i5, I5">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <east><JibsAmbulance /></east>
                        <west><PharmacyMain /></west>
                        <north><GrocerParkingLot /></north>
                </exits>
        </PharmacyParkingLot>
        
        <JibsParkingLotExit name="Parking lot exit, jibs lot exit, k4, K4">
                <ldesc>This lot is much less crowded. You can hear some strange music coming from the carnival across the street. 
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><Jibs /></south>
                        <east><MainStreetFour /></east>
                        <west>The doors to this ambulance have been welded shut...can't go this way</west>
                </exits>
        </JibsParkingLotExit>
        
        <GrocerParkingLot name="Grocery parking lot, grocer lot, i4, I4">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><PharmacyParkingLot /></south>
                        <north><GrocerEntrance /></north>
                        <east>The doors to this ambulance have been welded shut...can't go this way</east>
                </exits>
        </GrocerParkingLot>
        
        <PharmacyMain name="Pharmacy entrance, pharmacy main, h5, H5">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><PharmacyBehindCounter /></north>
                        <east><PharmacyParkingLot /></east>
                </exits>
        </PharmacyMain>
        
        <PharmacyBehindCounter name="Behind the pharmacy counter, pharmacy counter, behind counter, h4, H4">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><PharmacyMain /></south>
                        <west>Through the window you can see the Elementary School's playground across the alley. Things over there are too quiet now. Better avoid it.</west>
                </exits>
        </PharmacyBehindCounter>
        
        <GrocerEntrance name="Grocery entrance, the grocery, i3, I3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><GrocerParkingLot /></south>
                        <west><ProduceSection /></west>
                        <east><TwinkySection /></east>
                </exits>
        </GrocerEntrance>
        
        <ProduceSection name="The produce section, produce, h3, H3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <east><GrocerEntrance /></east>
                </exits>
        </ProduceSection>
        
        <TwinkySection name="The snack section, snacks, twinkies, j3, J3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north>The grocery's front door is barricaded from the inside. Maybe there was...or is someone in here...with me.</north>
                        <west><GrocerEntrance /></west>
                        <east><Butchery /></east>
                </exits>
        </TwinkySection>
        
        <Butchery name="The butchery, butcher, carniceria, k3, K3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><TwinkySection /></west>
                        <east>The emergency exit is also barricaded. It's pretty creepy in here, better hurry and retrace my steps out.</east>
                </exits>
        </Butchery>
        
<!--######################### MAIN STREET CLASSES ##################################DONE--> 

        <MainStreetOne name="Main street exit, main street one, l1, L1">
                <ldesc>This is the city limit for your little town and it has been barricaded with two or three large semis. Downtown, and maybe your 
                        family, are to the north. There is a small path leading into the hills the west. Main Street continues to the south.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north>Beyond the highway barricade you can see that downtown is in flames and the streets are thick with the Undead. Your future doesn't lay that way.</north>
                        <west>The note you found earlier told you to head to the shore to the east. There will time for exploring later.<!--HillsSeven /--></west>
                        <south><MainStreetTwo /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetOne>

        <MainStreetTwo name="Main street and 1st avenue, main street two, l2, L2">
                <ldesc>Outside the entrance to the carnival. The city is quaking with the shuffling and moaning of the undead, better get of the main street soon.
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetOne /></north>
                        <west> <!--FirstAveEight /-->The rest of town isn't ready for you yet..You should stay on the east side.</west>
                        <east><BWParkingLotOne /></east>
                        <south><MainStreetThree /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetTwo>
        
        <MainStreetThree name="Main street at Grocery, main street three, l3, L3">
                <ldesc>The grocery store has an entrance to the west. The city is quaking with the shuffling and moaning of the undead, better get of the main street soon.
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetTwo /></north>
                        <west>You charge the door but it doesn't budge. Better keep moving.</west><!--############################# Forest/Graveyard/Swamp Classes ###################--> 
                        <south><MainStreetFour /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetThree>
        
        <MainStreetFour name="Main street and grocery lot entrance, main street one, l4, L4">
                <ldesc>The fast food parking lot entrance is the the west. The city is quaking with the shuffling and moaning of the undead, better get of the main street soon.
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetThree /></north>
                        <west><JibsParkingLotExit /></west>
                        <south><MainStreetFive /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetFour>
        
        <MainStreetFive name="Main street at Jack in the Box, main street five, l5, L5">
                <ldesc>The rollercoaster from the carnival has crashed and spilled out onto the street blocking access to the rest of main street.
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetFour /></north>
                        <south>The wreckage prevents you from continuing south. There's probably a way around.</south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetFive>
                
        <MainStreetSix name="Main street and hospital lot entrance, main street six, l6, L6">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><HospitalParkingLot /></west>
                        <north>Part of the rollercoaster wreckage has blocked access to the rest of Main Street. Maybe there is a way around.</north>
                        <south><MainStreetSeven /></south>
                        <east>The fence is too high to climb, plus that rollercoaster wreckage doesn't look to safe to hang around. Better find another way.</east>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetSix>
        
        <MainStreetSeven name="Main street at Hospital, main street seven, l7, L7">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetSix /></north>
                        <south><MainStreetEight /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetSeven>
        
        <MainStreetEight name="Main street and 2nd avenue, main street eight, l8, L8">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetSeven /></north>
                        <west>The houses to the west have been burned to the ground and the mansion on the hill beyond them seems to be emitting a sinister orchestral tune. You've got no time for psychos better not head that way!<!--SecAveEight /--></west>
                        <south><MainStreetNine /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetEight>
        
        <MainStreetNine name="Main street and Zoo entrance, main street nine, l9, L9">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetEight /></north>
                        <east><!--ZooParkingLotOne /-->The zoo gates are locked tight...maybe we will see zombie sharks...in the sequel...</east>
                        <south><MainStreetTen /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetNine>
        
        <MainStreetTen name="Main street end, main street ten, l10, L10">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetNine /></north>
                        <!--west><HouseFourBY /></west-->
                        <south><CountryRoadOne /></south>
                </exits>
        </MainStreetTen>
        
        <CountryRoadOne name="Dirt road, country road one, l11, L11">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><MainStreetTen /></north>
                        <west>That ditch looks pretty unforgiving.You should avoid it.</west>
                        <south><CountryRoadTwo /></south>
                        <east><SwampOne /></east>
                </exits>
        </CountryRoadOne>
        
        <SwampOne name="Swamp trail, m11, M11">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><CountryRoadOne /></west>
                        <south>The muck is too deep to go that way</south>
                        <north>The muck is too deep to go that way..and something smells.</north>
                </exits>
        </SwampOne>
        
        <CountryRoadTwo name="Dirt road in deep woods, country road two, l12, L12">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><CountryRoadOne /></north>
                        <south>The forest is too dense to continue south.</south>
                        <west>The forest is too dense to continue west.</west>
                        <east><CountryRoadThree /></east>
                </exits>
        </CountryRoadTwo>
        
        <CountryRoadThree name="Muddy path in deep woods, country road three, m12, M12">
                <ldesc>TBD
                        
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><CountryRoadTwo /></west>
                        <north>The mud is too thick to walk through, better stay on the path.</north>
                        <south><MilitarySafeZone /></south>
                </exits>
        </CountryRoadThree>
        
        <MilitarySafeZone name="Military safe zone, military camp, m13, M13">  <!--POSSIBLE ENDING HERE************************************************************-->
                <ldesc>You stumble through the trees out into a clearing and are shocked by the bright sun. You are dizzy for a moment but after your eyes 
                        adjust a smile bursts onto your face. The clearing is filled with soldiers with huge guns and they are shepherding civilians to various 
                        relief tents. You are approached by one of the soldiers.
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><CountryRoadThree /></north>
                </exits>
        </MilitarySafeZone>
        
<!--########################### Boardwalk Classes ##################################-->
        
        <BWParkingLotOne name="The carnival parking lot, boardwalk parking lot, m2, M2">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWParkingLotTwo /></north>
                        <west><MainStreetTwo /></west>
                </exits>
        </BWParkingLotOne>
        
        <BWParkingLotTwo name="Carnival ticket booths, boardwalk ticket booths, m1, M1">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <east><BWShopsTwo /></east>
                        <south><BWParkingLotOne /></south>
                </exits>
        </BWParkingLotTwo>
        
        <BWShopsTwo name="Ye olde shoppes, creepy pac sun, n1, N1">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><BWParkingLotTwo /></west>
                        <south><HauntedHouseGame /></south>
                </exits>
        </BWShopsTwo>
        
        <HauntedHouseGame name="Ye olde Haunted House, creepy house tho, n2, N2">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWShopsTwo /></north>
                        <south><CarnyGames /></south>
                </exits>
        </HauntedHouseGame>
        
        <CarnyGames name="Boardwalk carny games, n3, N3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><HauntedHouseGame /></north>
                        <south><RollerCoasterControls /></south>
                </exits>
        </CarnyGames>
        
        <RollerCoasterControls name="Carnival rides control box, n4, N4">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <west><RollerCoaster /></west>
                        <east><BWEntrance /></east>
                        <south><FerrisWheel /></south>
                        <north><CarnyGames /></north>
                </exits>
        </RollerCoasterControls>
        
        <RollerCoaster name="Rollercoaster wreckage, m4, M4">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <east><RollerCoasterControls /></east>
                        <west>You can see the hospital grounds through the fence. It seems like its been days since you woke up.</west>
                </exits>
        </RollerCoaster>
        
        <FerrisWheel name="The save-Ferris Wheel, n5, N5">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><RollerCoasterControls /></north>
                </exits>
        </FerrisWheel>
        
        <BWEntrance name="Beach side boardwalk entrance, o4, O4">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWOne /></north>
                        <south><ClownRoom /></south> <!--SHOULD BE LOCKED AND SHIT-->
                        <west><RollerCoasterControls /></west>
                        <east>The ocean is lapping gently at the shore. You're hit with a pang of sadness. The world used to be so simple. Better keep moving</east>
                </exits>
        </BWEntrance>
        
        <BWOne name="Beach side boardwalk, o3, O3">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWTwo /></north>
                        <south><BWEntrance /></south>
                        <east>The ocean is lapping gently at the shore. You're hit with a pang of sadness. The world used to be so simple. Better keep moving</east>
                </exits>
        </BWOne>
        
        <BWTwo name="Boardwalk bathrooms, o2, O2">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWElectricBox /></north>
                        <south><BWOne /></south>
                        <east>The ocean is lapping gently at the shore. You're hit with a pang of sadness. The world used to be so simple. Better keep moving</east>
                </exits>
        </BWTwo>
        
        <BWElectricBox name="Boardwalk electric panel, o1, O1">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <south><BWTwo /></south>
                        <east>The ocean is lapping gently at the shore. You're hit with a pang of sadness. The world used to be so simple. Better keep moving</east>
                </exits>
        </BWElectricBox>
        
        <ClownRoom name= "The carnival supply room, the clown room, o5, O5">
                <ldesc>TBD
                
                </ldesc>
                <exits>
                        <north><BWEntrance /></north>
                        <east>Through the cracked, dusty window you can see a huge oil rig offshore. The vessel has lights on. Maybe someone survived after all.</east>
                </exits>
        </ClownRoom>
        
                        
<!--SwampOne in MainStreet############################# Forest/Graveyard/Swamp Classes ###################-->         
<!-- ############################ 1st Avenue Classes ################################DONE-->

<!--To be completed later  ########################### Alley Classes ######################################-->

<!--########################### Zoo Classes ########################################-->
<!--############################# Hills/ Lake/ Cabin Classes #######################-->
<!--################################## Mansion/Houses Classes ######################-->
<!--###############################Elementary School Classes #######################-->
<!--############################# Construction Site/ Field Classes #################-->  
<!--Brandon's Rooms-->
<!--Steve's Rooms-->
<!--Zack's Rooms-->             
</rickGame>
<!--brandonGame xmlns:props="pyf.props">
</brandonGame>
<steveGame xmlns:props="pyf.props">
</steveGame>
<zackGame xmlns:props="pyf.props">
</zackGame-->
